export const QuizData = [
  {
    id: 0,
    question: `Which countries have bombed the American at Pearl Harbour?`,
    options: [`Empire of Japan`, `German`, `Soviet`, `France`],
    answer: `Empire of Japan`,
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    question: `Who is the only one that can solve Nazi encripted code?`,
    options: [`Rommel`, `Herman Goerring`, `Winston Churchill`, `Alan Turing`],
    answer: `Alan Turing`,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: `Which countries Hitler didn't invade?`,
    options: [`Poland`, `Italy`, `France`, `Czechoslovakia`],
    answer: `Italy`,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: `Who remain neutral ground when it comes to a war`,
    options: [`Switzerland`, `Turkey`, `Spain`, `England`],
    answer: `Switzerland`,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: `Who is supposed to be successor after Lenin died`,
    options: [`Stalin`, `Gorbachev`, `Khrushchev`, `Trotsky`],
    answer: `Trotsky`,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: `What year is the end of World War 2`,
    options: [`1935`, `1938`, `1941`, `1945`],
    answer: `1945`,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: `What is most bloodiest place in WW2 that leads to Nazi's greatest defeat`,
    options: [`Leningrad`, `Stalingrad`, `Moscow`, `Nagasaki`],
    answer: `Stalingrad`,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: `Which one of these provinces did American drop the bomb`,
    options: [`Nagasaki`, `Bangkok`, `Tokyo`, `Normandy`],
    answer: `Nagasaki`,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: `Which countries have lost the most ammount of people in WW2`,
    options: [`Soviet`, `German`, `Italy`, `England`],
    answer: `Soviet`,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: `Who said the word "We have defeated the wrong enemy"`,
    options: [`Roosevelt`, `Hirohito`, `George S. Patton`, `Rommel`],
    answer: `George S. Patton`,
  },
];
